linkhello.com 2013-10-10

# None

###### About linkhello Privacy

This policy explains how linkhello treats personal information that linkhello collects and receives when an individual or business becomes a linkhello member or partner. Personal information is information that is personally identifiable like your name, address, birth date, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.  
This policy applies only to linkhello and does not apply to the practices of companies that linkhello does not own or control or to people that linkhello does not employ or manage. In addition, certain linkhello associated companies have their own privacy statements which can be viewed by going to their websites.

###### General Information

linkhello collects personal information such as your name, email address, business name, and country you reside in, when you register for our services. linkhello may also collect other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. Once you register with linkhello and sign in to our services, your personal information will only be available to us and will remain anonymous to other linkhello members. 

###### Security 

linkhello takes precautions to ensure that member account information is kept private. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal or business related data.   
Please note however that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. 

###### Information Sharing and Disclosing

As otherwise described in this privacy statement, linkhello will not disclose any personal information to a third party, except if any situation arises and linkhello believes disclosure is necessary. The following are exceptions: 

  * linkhello will conform to any legal requirements, respond to a subpoena, search warrant or any other legal process received, whether or not a response is required by applicable law
  * linkhello also reserves the right to exchange any personal information to any related companies.
  * linkhello will enforce the linkhello "Terms of Agreement" to protect our rights; and to protect the safety of members of the public and users of [linkhello.com](http://www.linkhello.com/)
  * linkhello reserves the right to transfer personal information to any successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of linkhello or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest.

If you have any concern about your personal information, please feel free to contact us, and we will assist you with any concerns. 

###### Links

linkhello is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on linkhello. 

###### Cookies

_What is a cookie?_

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. 

_Choices about Cookies_  
You can configure your browser to accept or reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences). In order to take advantage of [linkhello.com](http://www.linkhello.com/) and to use most functions on [linkhello.com](http://www.linkhello.com/), you must enable cookies from [linkhello.com](http://www.linkhello.com/). 

_Why does[linkhello.com](http://www.linkhello.com/) use cookies?_  
linkhello uses its own cookies for a number of reasons. linkhello uses cookies to store members' preferences and to record session information. linkhello can access your information when you "sign in," so that we can provide you with a customized content. linkhello can estimate and report our total audience size and traffic and conduct research to improve linkhellos content and services. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

_Third Party Advertisers and cookies_  
linkhello uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this website, other Web sites, and other forms of media in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

###### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

linkhello reserves the right to make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of the changes that have been made. linkhello members are bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. 

###### Questions and Suggestions

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.
